brightstarcorp.com 2006-06-15

# Become A Customer

| 

Privacy Statement  

Brightstar recognizes privacy and security as being a concern for most individuals accessing the Internet. Whether you're buying one of our quality products, or just browsing our site, we want to make you comfortable with our privacy practices and the security measures we take to protect your personal information. **This statement discloses the privacy guidelines for Brightstar consumer Web sites. Information submitted solely in a business capacity is not covered by these guidelines.** Please read our guidelines to understand the following: 

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by Brightstar as set forth in the policy currently in effect. If we decide to change our policy, such changes will be posted here on the Web site, so please check back periodically to ensure you have the most current policy. 

**What information is collected?**

When a visitor places an order with us, Brightstar may collect personally identifiable information, including name, title, company, address, e-mail address, phone numbers, social security numbers, driver's license numbers, date of birth. We do not require this information to obtain access to any part of our public site, but do require it if you wish to place an order, or set up an account for software downloads. 

In addition to ordering and registration, we may ask you for and collect personal information at other times, including by way of example, when you enter a sweepstakes or contest or participate in a promotion, or marketing campaign sponsored by Brightstar or one of its business partners; when you want to find out about service offered in your area; when you complete surveys or other questionnaires; or when you send an e-mail to Brightstar. Wherever Brightstar collects personal information we try to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page. 

Our web server logs collect the domain names of visitors to our Web sites. This information is aggregated to measure number of visits, average time spent on a Brightstar Web site, pages viewed, etc. We use this information to measure the use of our sites and to improve the content of our sites. 

**What about cookies?**

When you come into our site, our server attaches a small text file to your hard drive -- a cookie. Your unique cookie tells us that it's you whenever you re-enter our site, so we can recall where you've previously been on our site, and what, if anything, you have in your shopping cart. Cookies help us deliver a better Web site experience to our users. 

Generally, we use cookies to: 

(1) Remind us of who you are and to access your account information (stored on our computers) in order to deliver to you a better and more personalized experience. 

(2) Determine the effectiveness of our e-commerce relationships. Brightstar's e-commerce partners and affiliate program use cookies to identify the sites from which a user enters our site. Users linking to the Brightstar site from one of our e-commerce partner or affiliate sites are given a unique cookie. This cookie identifies from which site the user linked to Brightstar. This information is used to determine the effectiveness of our relationships and to administrate our affiliate program. This information may also be used to help target advertisements based on user interests and behavior. 

(3) Assist Brightstar in tracking what items are in your shopping cart. 

(4) Track your progress and number of entries in some of our promotions, sweepstakes and contests. 

(5) Measure traffic patterns, and which areas of the Brightstar site you have visited, and your visiting patterns. This information collected by using a cookie is sometimes called "clickstream." We use this information to understand how our users navigate our site, and to determine common traffic patterns, including what site the user came from. We use this information to make site navigation and product recommendations, and to help redesign our site in order to make your experience on our site more efficient and enjoyable. We may also use this information to better personalize the content, banner ads, and promotions that you and other users will see. This helps Brightstar deliver you the content you want, in order for you to make better purchasing decisions. You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those services or engage in activities that require the placement of cookies. 

**Who is collecting the information?**

When you are on a Brightstar site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Brightstar, Corp., its subsidiaries and related companies. Additionally, if you purchase a cellular phone, pager or other device requiring service, your personal information may be collected by a third party vendor working with Brightstar. Brightstar may also contract with third party companies to perform services for Brightstar on its Web site that require these companies to collect personal information (e.g. hosting a Web site sweepstakes, promotion or survey, or selling software downloads). The Brightstar Web site may also contain various links to third-party Web sites. These sites may provide additional information, goods, services and/or promotions. These sites are owned and operated independently of Brightstar, and have their own separate privacy and data collection practices. Any information you provide to these Web sites will be governed under the terms of their privacy policy, if any. Brightstar has no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the independent actions or policies of these independent sites, and is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such sites. 

**How is my information used?**

Brightstar's primary goal in collecting personal information is to facilitate order processing and to enable us to contact you if a problem arises with your order. Additionally, if you purchase a cellular phone or other device requiring service, your personal information may be used to obtain a credit report if necessary. Providing such information when making a purchase is required. This information may also be used to provide you with a customized experience on our site, which includes interactive communications, and other services. 

The Brightstar site may also contain optional surveys and questionnaires asking for information, as well as several opportunities for visitors to ask questions. We use the information you provide to help us design and build better products, to customize your shopping experience, and to provide advice and purchase recommendations. Taking part in any of these segments is always optional. 

We also use the information we collect to help target valuable marketing and advertising offers. This kind of advertising may be done with banner ads as well as promotional e-mails sent by Brightstar, or by third parties under contract with Brightstar. Brightstar may also match user information with third party data to help us better understand our customers. This means Brightstar may combine the personal information you provide us with information available from other sources, including offline sources, to market new products or services we think may be of interest to you. 

Finally, Brightstar does research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior based on the information provided to us when making a purchase, during a promotion, from surveys and from our server log files. We do this to better understand and serve our users. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis so as to prevent identification of personal information relating to any one individual. Brightstar may share this aggregated data with our business partners. 

**With whom does Brightstar share my information?**

Except as outlined in this policy or on our Web site, Brightstar never provides your personal information to third parties without your consent. Brightstar shares the information you provide with Brightstar subsidiaries and related companies. If you purchase a cellular phone or other device requiring service, your personal information is shared with the service provider/carrier with which you subscribe. Additionally, if you express an interest in a product requiring a particular type of service, Brightstar may share your personal information with your local service provider in order to determine whether such service is available in your area. 

Brightstar may also share your personal information with third-party business partners so that they may provide services to Brightstar that are consistent with the terms of this Privacy Policy, and this Web site (e.g. database management, sending targeted e-mails, software sales, and conducting sweepstakes and other promotions on behalf of Brightstar). Brightstar takes great pride in utilizing only reputable business partners. Brightstar may also, on occasion, provide personally identifiable information to third-party businesses as part of a specific product, service, or promotion. 

Brightstar's Web site may also utilize third party vendors to provide products and services directly to Brightstar consumers. Such relationships are designated with a "Provided by Company" legend or logo, or other similarly worded designation. If you desire to purchase a product or service from such third party, your personal information will be collected by the third-party company, and shared with Brightstar. You may review the privacy practices of the third party either by clicking the link on the bottom of the page, or by clicking on the "Provided by Company" logo, which will take you to their Web site. Additionally, when you purchase or download software applications from Brightstar or a third party, your personal information is shared with the software developer/licensor in order to register you as a licensed software user, and to permit them to provide you any required support. Although these software developers are encouraged to develop and follow appropriate privacy policies, Brightstar cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of such companies. If you are concerned about the privacy policy of a certain developer or software company, you may contact them directly or visit their individual Web sites. 

Brightstar may also disclose personal information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating this site's Terms of Use or may be violating Brightstar's or other's rights or causing injury to or interference with Brightstar's or other's property. Brightstar may also disclose or access personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

Brightstar may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our Web site to prospective business partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. 

What choices do I have regarding collection, use and distribution of my information? 

Brightstar or its business partners may, from time to time, send you e-mail or direct mail regarding our products and services. If you do not want to receive such information, simply tell us when you give us your personal information, or follow the directions contained on it to remove your name from our mailing list. 

On certain types of Brightstar promotions, we will ask for your e-mail address in order to contact you in the event you have won a prize. When you participate in these types of promotions, you may receive promotion-related e-mail. Occasionally these promotion-related e-mail messages may include targeted advertisements. If you do not wish to receive such advertisements, you can choose not to participate in such promotions or contests. 

If you ever have questions regarding an e-mail you receive from Brightstar or one our business partners, or want to be removed from a mailing list, please contact us at info@us.brightstarcorp.com. 

**What Security measures does Brightstar use to protect my information from loss, misuse or alteration?**

When you place an order or provide personal information, your transactions are encrypted for security. Encryption scrambles the information in your purchase, including your credit card number, so this information can only be viewed by Brightstar. 

Brightstar uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology, the highest level of security on the Internet. The SSL protocol provides server authentication, data integrity, and privacy on the Web. This security measure helps ensure that no impostors, eavesdroppers, or vandals get your personal information. SSL not only encrypts your personal and financial information transmitted, including credit card information, but also verifies the identity of the server and that the original message arrives safely at its destination. 

However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Brightstar cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our Web site, and therefore you use our site at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we use our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

As an international company Brightstar has international sites and users all over the world. When you give Brightstar personal information, that information may be sent electronically to servers outside of the country where you originally entered the information. In addition, that information may be used, stored and processed outside of the country where you entered that information. Whenever Brightstar handles personal information, regardless of where this occurs, it takes steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. 

**How can I correct or change my personal information?**

If you would like to review, correct or change any personal information you have provided, or remove your name from our mailing list, please e-mail us at info@us.brightstarcorp.com. If you have established a "user profile" on a Brightstar Web site, you may change the information you provided at anytime by visiting that portion of the Web site and resubmitting your information. 

**What about my child's privacy?**

This site is intended for use by persons over the age of 13. Brightstar does not seek to collect information about children under the age of 13\. No information should be submitted to or posted on this Web site by users under 13 years of age. If a child under the age of 13 submits personal information to this Web site, we delete the information as soon as we discover it and do not use it for any other purpose. Brightstar encourages parents to take an active role in their children's use of the Internet, and to inform them of the potential dangers of providing information about themselves over the Internet. 

**Additional Information.** Questions regarding this policy should be directed to info@us.brightstarcorp.com. You may also contact us by U.S. mail at: 

Brightstar 

1001 Technology Way

Libertyville, IL 60048
